
let questions = [
  {
    question: "Where would you put your document's <title>?",
    choice1: "<footer>",
    choice2: "<head>",
    choice3: "<hand>",
    choice4: "<body>",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following Jays is not web development?",
    choice1: "jQuery",
    choice2: "javaScript",
    choice3: "JJ Abrams",
    choice4: "JSON",
    answer: 3
  },
  {
    question: "Which is a fun way to learn CSS layouts?",
    choice1: "Flexbox Froggy",
    choice2: "Box-Size Betty",
    choice3: "Column Width Carl",
    choice4: "PaddingTop Bear",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Which is a way to comment HTML",
    choice1: "<!-- Comment --!>",
    choice2: "// Comment",
    choice3: "#comment",
    choice4: "@^&&--@$ Comment",
    answer: 1
  },
  {
    question: "Who does Blue Horseshoe love?",
    choice1: "Yoyodyne Propulsions",
    choice2: "Anacott Steel",
    choice3: "Blue Steel",
    choice4: "Tyrell Corporation",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Which browser do we use?",
    choice1: "Netscape Navigator",
    choice2: "AOL Desktop",
    choice3: "Wii Internet",
    choice4: "Google Chrome",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Which is NOT a javascript pop-up?",
    choice1: "confirm",
    choice2: "console.log",
    choice3: "prompt",
    choice4: "alert",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "Which is NOT a method to set variables?",
    choice1: "let",
    choice2: "const",
    choice3: "var",
    choice4: "man",
    answer: 4
  },
  {
    question: "Which is correct order, outside>in?",
    choice1: "object>padding>moat",
    choice2: "margin>border>padding>object",
    choice3: "padding>margin>border>object",
    choice4: "margin>gutter>object>padding",
    answer: 2
  },
  {
    question: "What is BootStrap?",
    choice1: "Line of Construction Themed Underwear",
    choice2: "Worst Pancake Syrup Ever",
    choice3: "Suite of CSS Tools",
    choice4: "What Your Dad Got Spanked By",
    answer: 3
  }
];

